# Vitaliy Polyanskiy (Full Stack Engineer)

**Skype:** vit.polyanskiy

**E-mail:** vit.polyanskiy@gmail.com

**Tel.:** +380 (99) 78- 36-817

Site: myfe.site

Linkedin: <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/vitaliy-polyanskiy-6930b515b/">https://www.linkedin.com/in/vitaliy-polyanskiy-6930b515b/</a>

#### Github:

• <a href="https://github.com/alreadyExisted">https://github.com/alreadyExisted</a>

• <a href="https://github.com/easy-boilerplates">https://github.com/easy-boilerplates</a>

## **Summary of qualifications:**

Front-end developer with a strong tech skill set and 4+ years of experience in the field of web-development.

Professional skills: native JavaScript, ES6+, TypeScript, ReactJS, Redux, RxJS, NodeJS, NextJS, PostgreSQL, Docker, WordPress, jQuery, HTML5, Pug, CSS3, SCSS, SASS, Stylus, Twitter Bootstrap, Gulp, Grunt, Webpack, Git, Mercurial, Jira, Confluence.

Pet projects (low) skills: NestJS, Angular 1, VueJS, GraphQL, MongoDB.

## **Experience:**

October 2016 - Present

Full Stack JS Developer at Simcord LLC

**Position:** full-time web-developer.

# **Responsibilities:**

- Development of Single Page Applications (SPA + SSR), websites according to specifications and mockups, teamwork.
- Support of existing web APPs and sites.
- Code review.
- Estimate of new projects and additional functionality.

# **Technologies and tools:**

native JavaScript, ES6, ReactJS, TypeScript, NodeJS, NextJS, RxJS, Recharts, D3, Websockets, PostgreSQL, Docker, HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, SASS, Stylus, Gulp,

Webpack, Git, Mercurial, Photoshop, Jira, Confluence.

Aug. 2015 – Sep. 2016 Web-developer at Startup

**Position:** remote full-time web-developer.

# **Responsibilities:**

- Development of websites according to specifications and mockups, teamwork.
- Support of existing web sites.

### **Technologies and tools:**

native JavaScript, jQuery, WordPress, HTML5, CSS3, SASS, Twitter Bootstrap, Gulp, Git, Photoshop.

#### Languages

English – reading technical documentation.

Ukrainian – native.

Russian – native.

#### Education

• 2010 - 2015, H.S. Skovoroda Kharkiv National Pedagogical University, obtained Master's degree in Physics, Computer Science.

#### Additional information

I've released in production over 30 websites.

I have experience in developing web applications (SPA + SSR) using such JavaScript frameworks as ReactJS, NextJS, NodeJS (Express).

Creation of code that is valid, cross-browser, rubber, and adaptive to different screen resolutions. Ability to work both in a team and independently. Purposeful, self-motivated, and sociable, able to work within strict deadlines, and think outside the box. I seek to constantly enhance my professional skills and adopt new practices that can benefit the quality of my work.